voicedailydeals.com 2017-06-24

# VOICE Daily Deals - Privacy Policy

## Voice Daily Deals

This Privacy Policy is effective as of January 9th, 2012

This Privacy Policy describes the practices that Voice Daily Deals ("Voice Daily Deals") follows with respect to the collection, maintenance and use of information submitted on deals.villagevoice.com (the "Site"). This Privacy Policy applies only to information we collect from this Site, and does not apply to any other website or business activity of Voice Daily Deals. By using our Site, and/or providing information to us, you consent to the collection, maintenance and use of this information by us.

If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site and exit immediately. We reserve the right to modify or amend the terms of this Privacy Policy from time to time. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to these terms means that you accept those changes. We will give you notice of the revised Privacy Policy by posting the revised policy on the Site and by revising the "effective date" set forth above.

## Information We Collect

We collect and maintain personally identifiable information and automatic information.

### Personally Identifiable Information

"Personally identifiable information" is information that tells us who you are, such as your name, screen name, email address, postal address, phone number, credit card information, birth date/year and gender.

Voice Daily Deals collects and maintains personally identifiable information about you only when you provide it to us. For example, we may collect and maintain personally identifiable information about you when you register for or participate in contests, sweepstakes, promotions, polls, surveys, newsletters and text messages (including contests, sweepstakes, promotions, polls, surveys, newsletters and text messages of certain third parties). We may also collect and maintain personally identifiable information when you post an ad, submit comments to the Site or letters to the editor, submit events for inclusion on our Site, purchase event tickets from us, or otherwise provide it to us when you contact us.

If you do not provide information to us, you may be unable to use certain features of the Site. For example, you cannot post comments in connection with certain articles or register for the Site, contests, surveys or newsletters unless you provide certain information. Also, you will not be able to submit events for inclusion on our Site or purchase event tickets if you do not provide certain information.

## Automatic Information and Cookies

"Automatic information" is information automatically collected by our web server (which may be hosted by a third party) that your web browser makes available whenever you visit our Site, such as your browser type and capabilities, network properties, the site that you visited before viewing our Site, content viewed on the Site, and your geographic location. We maintain such data in aggregated form; it is not associated with your IP address or personally identifiable information.

IP address tracking: All computers and servers on the Internet use IP addresses to recognize and communicate with each other. We collect and maintain IP addresses to administer and analyze our Site and report aggregate information (such as how many visitors we have and how many visitors see and click on particular advertisements).

We may associate your IP address with your personally identifiable information and may maintain, use and disclose such information in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy below.

Cookies: This Site also uses "cookies." "Cookies" are small text files that allow websites to store and retrieve information about you from your computer system. Voice Daily Deals does serve cookies to track individual site usage for later aggregation, but does not use cookies in order to retrieve any information from your computer other than information originally sent in a Voice Daily Deals cookie, such as a user code. We have no control over whether and how our advertisers use cookies that originate from their website or other websites. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, but you may not be able to take full advantage of our Site's features if you do.

We do not and cannot use cookies or IP address tracking to retrieve personally identifiable information from your computer.

## Use and Disclosure of Information

We maintain and use personally identifiable information for the purpose or purposes for which it is provided. For example, we may maintain and use personally identifiable information to send newsletters and text messages; to establish your online account and recognize you when you return to the Site; to contact you regarding contests, promotions, polls, and surveys; to complete the sale of event tickets; to provide customer support; or to otherwise communicate with you regarding our Site, an ad you posted, an event you submitted to the Site, or your comments or letters to the editor. If you do not wish to receive these communications, you may opt-out or unsubscribe by updating your preferences in your profile.

We may also maintain and use your personally identifiable information to attribute your comments, letters to the editor and/or other submissions to the Site to you. As has traditionally been the case with our print editions, we may require that you supply certain information to us (such as your real name, daytime telephone number and/or e-mail address) in connection with comments and other submissions to the Site. That is because we may need to contact you, and because your identity may be important to understand your point of view. If you send us comments or other submissions, we reserve the right to publish them in print or display them on this Site in full or in edited form. We normally honor requests to withhold your name and address when provided in connection with comments and other submissions, both in print and on-line, but we reserve the right to use, discuss and report facts that we consider newsworthy relating to submissions even if it might reveal or tend to reveal the poster's identity.

From time to time, we may send you information with announcements and updates about the Site and Voice Daily Deals and our partners.

We may disclose personally identifiable information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may have breached our Terms of Use or who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property, other users of our Site, or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities. We may also disclose personally identifiable information when we reasonably believe that the law requires it.

If you chose to provide your personally identifiable information for the purposes of a third-party contest, promotion, poll, survey or newsletter, your personally identifiable information will be given to Voice Daily Deals and to the third-party advertiser/sponsor involved with the relevant contest, promotion, poll, survey or newsletter and/or its agents and affiliates. To the extent the contest, promotion, poll, survey or newsletter has its own terms that conflict with the terms of this Privacy Policy, the terms of the contest, promotion, poll, survey, or newsletter govern.

We occasionally have third party agents, subsidiaries, affiliates and joint ventures that perform functions on our behalf, such as credit card processing, shipping or stocking orders, providing customer service, etc. They are provided access to personal information needed to perform their functions.

In the event of a sale of Voice Daily Deals or a sale of substantially all Voice Daily Deals' assets, personally identifiable information may be one of the business assets transferred or sold.

We may maintain and use automatic information to track how our visitors use the Site, study traffic patterns, and run and maintain the site, and may provide targeted advertisements to you based on such data.

Although we do not currently engage in such practices, Voice Daily Deals may in the future disclose automatic information to advertising networks that may use such information in connection with erecting and displaying targeted advertisements both on our website and on unaffiliated websites.

We may share aggregated data with our advertisers.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to any information you choose to make public.

## Opt-Out

You may terminate any ongoing communications you receive from Voice Daily Deals via e-mail (such as newsletters, subscriptions, contest results, survey inquiries, etc.) by (1) clicking the "unsubscribe" link that is available within the communication received, or (2) through your online profile.

## Children

Some of the material on this Site is for mature audiences, and parents and guardians should take responsibility for monitoring their children's use of the Site. Children under the age of 13 should not use this Site. We do not intentionally collect personally identifiable information from users of the Site who are under the age of thirteen.

## Links to Other Sites

This Site provides links to websites maintained by other organizations. Voice Daily Deals provides these links as a convenience to users, but it does not operate, control or endorse such sites. Voice Daily Deals also disclaims any responsibility for the information on those sites and any products or services offered on such sites. Please review the privacy policies of these sites. Voice Daily Deals is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties, and does not make any warranties or representations that any linked sites (or even this Site) will function without error or interruption, that defects will be corrected, or that the sites and their servers are free of viruses and other problems that can harm your computer. Voice Daily Deals disclaims any responsibility for transactions conducted on those sites and cannot vouch for the security of the information submitted in those transactions.

## E-Commerce and Our Secure Server

We use reasonable efforts to protect your personally identifiable information from unauthorized use or disclosure. Unfortunately, information transmitted on the Internet and/or stored on systems attached to the Internet are not 100% secure. As a result, we do not ensure, warrant or guarantee the security or integrity of such information. We will not be responsible for disclosure of any information due to errors in transmission or the unauthorized acts of third parties.

## Updates and Changes to Your Information.

If your personally identifiable information changes, you may correct and/or update it by sending us an email at community@villagevoice.com. You may also view, correct and/or update your personally identifiable information by accessing your profile on the Site.

## More Questions?

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please e-mail them to privacyadministrator@villagevoicemedia.com, and be sure to indicate the specific site you are visiting and the nature of your question or concern.

© 2011 Village Voice Media Holdings, LLC. All rights reserved
